shared.sx 2015-05-10

# shared.sx – innovative media-hosting solution

shared.sx takes your personal privacy serious.  
We will not disclose any personal information about you without your prior approval.  
In general, any information you provide to our team while contacting us will only be used within shared.sx. 

>   * **IP addresses of users**  
>  Our servers can detect the IP address of your browser according to Internet-technology.  
>  This IP address is registered by shared.sx servers especially for our internal use (registration of use,  
>  optimal downloads use and so on). These information are stored encrypted in our systems. 
>   * **E-Mail**  
>  Our server writes in the register of shared.sx users emails only for their registration and calculation.  
>  Under no circumstances will shared.sx lease, sell, or provide your personal information to any companies. 
>   * **Cookies use**  
>  shared.sx uses cookies for the users' comfort in order to save the browser settings.  
>  shared.sx does not use any methods for tracking users (the so-called "spy" or "1x1" gif images and so on). 
>   * **Safe operation with files**  
>  We have taken the appropriate security measures at the servers' physical location to protect from loss, incorrect usage, or change of information provided to us by the users of the service.  
>  Files, saved for delivery can be accessible only to shared.sx representatives or via a link provided to the recipient.  
>  All files saved by our service are deleted after a certain time period if you do not delete them yourself. 
>   * **Advertisements**  
>  Advertisements located on our website can be posted by third party advertisement company.  
>  These companies can use the information regarding your visits on these or other web pages  
>  (your name, address, e-mail, and phone number are excluded) to place an advertisement of products  
> and services that might be interesting to you. 
>   * **Inflicting**  
>  We can disclose your personal information in case it becomes necessary to defend our juridical rights.  
>  Especially if your information is connected with tangible or assumed saboteur actions  
>  or poses a potential threat to any personal's physical safety.  
>  Disclosure of your information can be lawful or as a result of a legal process. 
> 

We reserve the right to add, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy at any time.  
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us here.
